okay thank you thank you so like many
buddhist classes this is a kind of a
depressing class the desire to stop our
future lives and the anticipations of
taking future lives there's a
misperception misinterpretation without
this subject people come to this
conclusion well this is the Karma's are
not really helping really in our
philosophical thinking future lifespan
from this endless suffering and so part
of the idea of stopping it's almost like
the disgust times I was reading you know
I didn't know I was going to do this
until today so I really like
it'll read some of the verses apart
offensive Foley's on the very much
spring the crux of the course of this
class is to stop the desire for having
classes now skipped
think over and over how deeds and their
fruits never fail Thank You Reuben ah
that's tight in the cycles you sweet are
divine dressing we must stop the desire
for our future life so in that context
right the desire for the future we you
know I hope my future verse can can
really get into a realm that's going to
be pleasurable we know that there are
different realms of existence can
distinct was yeah so we're in the desire
realm correct missin embarrassed as a
form and foremost realm within I around
these different aspects that include
lower than human and higher than human
in our context of wanting to be born in
one of those in a sense be removed from
our suffer we really want to be born in
one of these rooms in certain traditions
bye for now
a lot of meditations or life years
millions of be kind of related sometimes
to the Christian heaven but we know in
our in our teaching so we know in the in
the teachings of the Wheel of Life
these realms will completely end into
much lower and then we see the amount
desire is probably the the launchpad and
the best instrument to get enlightened
in one a lifetime to remove the
suffering or more promise but that's not
the case we don't want to go there so to
get this idea of I'm tired is the first
in the process of karma we must learn
the correlations of of karma and how it
functions a great job on the power point
again thank you thank Akane destination
new powerpoints Elysium asked us so the
laws of karma who can tell me the first
one become a disaster karma cassettes
Lennon yeah you can say like it makes
like we are here that you
plant a seed to find a partner and
motivation and the fertilization
delivers it to you
similar result you take your own it's
the the actual action that will create
the seeds for you to find the partner
and it's not what is your intention
about to embark on so in that sense you
know we keep it basic in DCI we say you
know do a banana plantation you get
banana like makes like you know the
function of karma I said earlier you're
talking to a lot of you that were here
that it's more subtle than understanding
emptiness can be designed for your
future you can design what you want to
walk into six months from now
you're conscious of it or not in this
room right now so I don't know sit back
and understand that your seeds got you
in this room these are so extraordinary
since it's the Dharma somehow or another
you you know all of us should build on
for the ultimate goal master plan I
don't know I don't you know I know
I don't know my past lives we bring you
back and give you like makes like is
such a quintessential Eureka and that's
not complicated for step or step idea
proof of that and they always say when
we're on tour how many people that show
up in a 2000 because some other series
that don't allow them to actually break
we're all standing there to answer
questions my partner or business around
shift
in it in that moment you've done your
job they just want to tell you in this
beautiful Museum given detects point
really - yes - mitad fish cannot see us
becoming massive oil in a way that's the
reward the teacher that's a big deal in
a good way proud of these laws are a
foundation to all of our lives which is
the antidote to lessen the resources so
yes like makes like life is exactly
she's good results come from good deeds
okay I gave this a common comments
cassettes it does mean I guess the
plants kind of Ananas vaccine so karma
increases exponentially karma makes
expedition likes to use this idea that
there should have been oats Canady D
because at the waiters test they in Cana
test if a waiter doesn't understand a
word
it's justice I refuse it
that's what I was thinking at the word
exponentially I thought how many people
if you went to a restaurant what's wrong
my eggs a little bit more quickly a
better word this was for exponents you
maybe expand
that's not listing explosive exclude
when we taught this course into 2017 of
January I see Michael said okay every 24
hours pull together an idea and you
plant the seed you do the first step to
Fox a person who I don't know when you
did the numbers it was 31 trillion it's
my number
Wow seeds right now are right that's
right
every aspect of your conscious reality
did not Specter thanks Alice to see
search makes release Alice present
unpleasant neutral happening in 65 like
a mile aspasia to be a good meditation
what happened I know that soy
the sign on the bottom what students are
in the buy box via sign a really Tina
all of you would do it someday makes the
whole box
what Moxie segunda body commish a seed
by giving blood sample Judy you know
Jesse Mike was giving tons away I mean
personal was showing us that's a house
but I don't know I can't think well you
know basically what he's doing macht is
we talk about endowments for our
nonprofits could we raise five or ten
million dollars worry about spending our
precious time raising money and so when
he's on tour he'll give thousands of
dollars away enough how will
exponentially double every single day
it's been twice
the sky's the limit here yes the hits in
what what do you want less missed well I
don't know I I want I want to stick
around and see what happens for the next
25 years
jennifer franciotti he also seemed
associate this is the most exciting
thing on the planet to me this is
finished the simpler Santa Steve of the
campus beautiful minds in mine and
Salman is severity momentous cancelled a
little bit threatening as matter I see
on we as practitioners Steve I'm sorry
60 second a is this array we get a
factor of change in possibility for you
succeeding if a business is defendant
current when with EP booster disarming
plans for the benefit of others like
Somalia and how do we begin the practice
of in the wrong way you get the idea
I mean now we're talking nuclear power
yes make money I thought I climb it not
there I recommend once second your
thoughts going through the off top
ticket won't be good to control that
fact that are creating negative we're
going round
mrs. Grose's answer our leader is up the
symmetry line many sons are in wrong
tree issues declining said you know
begin to manifest in unpleasant form
biasing on some leading site is tiny it
was like like a tunic for me it was like
fantastic like my body was a key from
the other two class my god some kind of
beautiful seeds this one wound about a
salmon cup of weird voice that's how I
get common teaching you know toughest
classes and exponents Elif acted like
that happened Bank on that being a
component of when I was teaching maybe a
month and a half or two months ago next
so there's this idea also that if
nineteen this house everyday mental kind
of madness this is interesting because
it gets into expectations in life you
know the links that how many
disappointments have we had in the last
I don't know year
but why why do we have patients that we
assume well happy and happen if we do
certain things as simplified as the four
steps are its formula it's almost like a
mathematical theory of relativity and
it's easy and it works be disappointed
when we don't get what we want we rush
it should arrive get disappointed
because and so this is this is what
comes about if you didn't do the Karma
there's a debate in my mind about that
because our own plans
we're creating firms right now we are
Creon yet see as it's a comma it's
happening right now it's yes I gave this
more Karma's me a comma right after this
is done wrong don't change DISA climate
momentum this fan noise comma it's like
we creat Karma's with body speech in
mind right yeah it's like a comma in our
actions we create Cronus with our speech
our most powerful basis in decaf toys
you are thinking it gets us in the most
desperate wins every retreat was one of
these like Yanni's the eyeopener's about
how the
auctioning of patterns of thoughts be
fine be my Nikita was so hard wired into
a sofa trotted incident consciousness
direct imposes on busy and a gente and
it would be funny because I'd be do i I
wouldn't be in deep subtle mind fulness
I'd be washing the dishes job I'm a posh
suddenly I would see the Watchers mind
watching a pattern of thought systems at
my face get down most of our Normandy
seems secure a long hot ET des Lynam I'm
laid off judging that person for like 45
years God wouldn't mention said food
foods again settimia champagne coming to
in text on blood 3d seconds and give an
image study guns inside hildine amend
and then multiples and humble of
necessary because when that begins them
I mean does not see and getting to erase
that pattern for good because she made a
momentous my cancer this is most how
solutions well done it's a machine-type
it was signed you go to first base this
incline and sansara to site rice if you
don't secure on one grants the sonken in
my three this one gravity be sticker and
so many ice the Chiefs obtain momentum
and the manager about already metatarsal
head estas I keep listening a Javanese
dustless positioning its resulting in
the so-called conventional world of
ordinary things washing dishes
especially the convention
the gun cementing a apart out of or
watched of meditation is Maha mudra
Dinoco by nicki bang this will be a
bathroom vanity try first off is kissing
suntan in debate processes missing the
mark some passing on some configure our
deepest fear so the third law of karma
is the staying calm is it is don't plant
the seed just mental kind and psalm in
plants and tricks we can endure small
air you know why didn't i get the
promotion at work
Madame Habib a father only speak tricky
why can't I afford you know a two-week
vacation in Bali Madame kanyi McKenzie
last license I don't know must Saudi
above I let you know just think of the
things that we would like or expect to
get or have thanked time anything in the
again I hate it or the deodand I
punished because Jesus our stuff forget
in India man Schneider system on does
this one and it only having money so the
mind doesn't have to worry about the
second sound was suffocation the same
guys see - or my voice at night and no
to catch a fish planet Francis hours
good I'm not interested in making
millions of dollars in tradition in
million
financially own an oil rod so 14 and if
you like so forget it happened
guns each month leading smashing Wendy's
on and my mom is like so good - flowers
start to type like okay we better double
down on over here Elvis asbestos
Panhandle more would have you give me a
cage but she's right
on snikt lies exactly McInerney why am I
so feelin vanish Ponte in your wallet -
hast killed or missed assignment mouth
Sushma near Boise salmon have eaten we
leave the fact that the behind the
scenes anxiety or the thing before the
sour stuff guild in Spanish an inch
punch Lankan - flan see this Sam is no
longer throwing the plants gate and that
is just a beautiful woman leading to its
fastest scariest after banks under to
invest years in karma so next generation
to Constance gave the son of person
tarnished for my good news assistance to
conceive this for mine deflation effect
is ventilated cotton biggest consider
select a result harnessed for mine we'd
like to accentuate the positive right
via CTV of class I'm in the karmic
course we talk about dirty white seeds
or stained crimson come across the
tracks license are consciously creating
clinic the school Thomas it has we grasp
we know we want some results you know we
want it yeah yeah boy I don't know yeah
we can do all the you know there's
something called Assizes did rice fee
under ski the deepest layer the oxen
soonest Lea there am finger is layer yet
profoundly involved in the emptiness of
the three hours Bobby chefs Mathias me
Delia - keep in the back of your mind at
least - night
in six months I'll have another 6,000
okay in six sex house that I in karma
stained their studies yeah you know I'm
gonna get a result
yeah I gave this and it's stained so
nitrogen that course we say common that
I take very few people can create
perfect seeds the sickness conveniently
babies the betadine spices come up dance
audience emptiness of everything that we
do by is initially very high with the
actual practice of seed planting whether
that's you know that Liam hide nothing
was too late
not just rejoicing and the Leah hide
late the Simon all finding her female
the best lay ahead first taste also cast
full SS army they do plans
yeah it's it's it's a process that we
learned it's a simple test in Milan and
what about the objects that we choose
these it's with an object to generate
C's guaranteed years old
salmon supplants said again oh yeah give
me an example of a high object so keep
my space and also P Act
say it again
with dimly a teacher an authentic
teacher yeah I know all kind always OPA
could sign see parents who said yeah
duska sucked yeah parents what about a
CI or Diamond Mountain shots with a CIO
don't you know sorta acip
it's a peer assessment besonders we you
know we don't in our in our system of hi
comic objects you don't some sustained
their horn commission objector we people
do their due diligence when they give
money away decency
if you give a dollar to ACIP a day
mentioned here in some ways saving some
part of a system that's bringing the
ancient manuscripts to all of that
process is fascinating merit of that
with your dollars you're indirectly
getting 10% you get bad karma to becomes
this you get the wisdom to becomes
device ID fifties from the outside if
you try figured out for everything that
we go by nine in Tolan or in a fancy
costs that he decided he buying
not including inflation of the Indian
rupee mean floods you on this initial
everybody's complaining about
see-through bar okay everybody gets
raises either becomes the investment you
make with the investiture Medina before
my cinema cause or two things have to be
smooth orbiting text design Doctors
Without Borders it's the only solace of
serving humanity has a high karmic
relationship to the select us dimension
in design who is commish's okay and so
karmic objects we have to think about
but is Commission and I think the other
thing that is very interesting
chemically is my sign part with my money
to pay taxes if you destroy ancestors a
great talent of people that know how to
create loopholes to avoid Pincus conceal
a creative men F&B month grant you know
that has to do also with the correlation
of honesty let's see on the le kites
atonement integrity you are responsible
that's a list in your system wherever
you are in the world creating no legal
assistance to avoid paying what the
responsible aspect of a citizen should
be doing for their country dynami
launched mention relationship karma we
have coral and soon ants comma slant the
first day disappear inclined
kinda created this for men we are
it's margarita it's funny there are
certain times in life with karma also
society humbly yeah the slim end at sea
hippie becoming I can roughly fifty
common in chop wounds or asleep justly
maybe that's it she said suddenly burst
into your exclude the intently company
sleep I'm told many steps in the process
of death beyond the stamps what happens
to your super-spicy admit dining salmon
what actually is going on vez peseta
what's happening inside karmically
that's your reality must precede commish
Medina really Tate everything is running
out
Alice Alice Caesar purpose I'll skip
disarming Yuri now being destroyed funny
very nice for closing town then all the
sins see hear taste touch and feel and
think is what you make students
assignments and office so this comes
into the whole point of what seed will
take you what karma is going to take you
very kiss creature the process bring
what the hits its ovation protests the
next rebirth dine dine in a second what
I since and this is where we
have to really work hard on that
permittivity happen on some some and a
button yeah
Geshe Michaels teacher used to watch the
New York State Lottery on Wednesday
nights because it used to be million
short miniskirt CAPTCHA prom it Mineo
and smile and they play all this you
know happy music sighing it's okay
that's what's gonna happen
mega sec does Perseid when those seeds
are finalizing and that fella kiss
Almondine all for the let's say beam
dickens next a name where you're going
by suggest where is that gonna take you
are you going to be fully engaged with
the controlling of that
fairly it had to do with the uncertainty
it now brings us to height brink it's
not on par for you inside if the skin
all its so good news is there's only
three questions
no security it's kind of enjoyable no
plan is failsafe it's a kind of blonde
any tighten come well that's depressing
mister sneakily need about new - laden
you should say no because so i know the
four steps i can decide
oldest son nine relish candy fish could
determine its design and I know exactly
how to navigate that I can do it HP
month uh song gate we have eighteen
courses and then another rating we can
kill this idea the sphere DCED Vitaly
Cohen for this life and beyond four DS
asleep on further now for the meantime
about middle agree that life has no
certainty and no security I'm still tool
does the symbol even kind of see how I
skipped yeah yeah no if I'm gonna wake
up tomorrow morning if I see WB the
whole does he have any
premonition moments in a cottage cheese
candlelight or no need to compensate if
I see somebody knocks down in half I
would be great in a way right and
they're meditations to say why don't you
see morning at 8:00 and then take a
meditation on sandy Bachman and let's
not mine and told yes some space but he
hadn't told me what do we actually sit
on the cushion and do a death meditation
and say you know what bottom set state
of schism monotone 45 tonight been hotel
dry fertile l4 possibility at or on of
death realistically than how we perceive
it this is normal evasive on naman I'm
healthy you know good yoga practice it's
my fuel girl yes good
I have Medicare and good any doctor
Negron physicians can eat not self so I
have another 10 years I obviously be
Shannon it's not we don't and we just
have to get usable that tomorrow morning
creates a mind space desk 9m guyzzz
fryer fry primal beginningless death
birth system Dinah
it opens something up in your mind
stream so in your toolkit you should
have a really good jazz matter in that
investigation agouti to this made it a
tsunami or a happen we visited vogelin
knocked on some tote this being
convinced also yet son Coco there's
something in our system called the
fourth flower in the DCI system DCI
system give the stiff your bloomin it's
the results of our comics in designing
what we're walking into after de let's
approve main issue that's why so again
bus yeah whoa via you know beyond San
Jose - no way before this is this
beautiful reality here in this room
Diplo materiality here in this matter
it's an enormous beautiful possibility
oh this is anyone - it was really driven
our first two marks was to leave marks
on and plants and environments but about
automated via a fan and fan and our visa
smitten completely couldn't be as design
and well we first want to get
enlightened in one lifetime
21:20 smelly Malloy that's me da
famously director a fan of the live
minty smell you from here in the room
what they do here but I'll be more than
50 percent home
Bambi still hustles faster than hidin
Vicky shaft um I just you know I bought
I took the kool-aid and I bought the
package and I really believe it's
possible that all of you in this room
have the potential in this lifetime to
get out happy be funny in the hunt sake
live for whoever shall hide in director
of the missus fistina misfit nice
mansion around me who has the same
orientation
silky now that roughing up so slight
summation first redesigning this is bit
suit Leroy and Selene don't have this
possibility it's good food adventure my
slides why Mika's son it's just if
you're here men do hippest you're
wondering a million this right now aside
nominal notice a guy knows it's a
million you gotta take the kool-aid ish
Galvez I want you to kind of think about
it more shall be assaulted after drew
been acting there's always in my world a
hesitation in - Jared Diamond Mountain -
Ricardo leaving home yeah happy right
high PR dilip up a sex toy business
backwater mind of mine seats my historic
it's not always a business of gauntlet
you know Simon offices I'm sorry mom I
know
- I'm Chang kiha ein Karem artisan
appeases Rondo boats betrayed this is
one ginam fear when I'm here
that's Philemon CC matochkin it's always
been there and aspire might after you
know all of I what I've done here and my
high they must see here illipe Tommy Mac
- dry Yanis retreat that happened again
when I arrived I was peeing on this
continent like I said truly come here
name and need sir pharmacies that ripen
here since I'm indecisive associate feel
uncomfortable because I'm going into
this other aspect of myself that is
extremely powerful on this aircraft for
heaith society I can ripen things here
on the Fela Fela sound arrived here I
will allow to happen and and those seeds
are either extraordinary or something
that I have to correct or fix these
salmon salmon dish parents might hard cm
tall a 4:3 image did wonders of this
planet to say how powerful a basis in
three Sun 20 crafts Foley sauce I
believe to 15 years to purify and once
you have them it better it will be
riding is this commish soldier mind Viet
foil hits a sinus can dine and guy
strange but not serious I'm just saying
chemically emission it's in a place at
the right side I'm sorry sighs you have
to take a combination from karma a
Mormon
Tifa Tolan won't be notes in hotel in
idea Hardwell made it here that we
talked about the ante salmon rice not be
quickened things can ripen in certain
places can sister and this is one of the
salmon cannon ambition Daniela ryf Oscar
hood here method sue in order to escape
the circle of life opening cries of the
sleeps so a beautiful wide actions plant
good seeds my sighs come on tiny
consequences for that's a formal way of
saying formally I don't face it
practically read if you comedy said sir
there's another aspect that's the
downside that's depressing T about
negative seeds diggity phenomenon God in
the realms of existence there are 10
skinny de la Sofia Buddhism they can say
philosophy that's what this talks about
you know the hell realms the code it's
not some self existent place it's right
here in this room but in the sense of
this idea of karma sense of what would
it take for us to realize good idea to
do a meditation on a lower realm nice
young okay I you know you know could I
do a Tong Lin on the beings that are
simultaneously I used to do a lot of hot
yoga like Bikram so it's 105 degrees and
you you sweat and I used to do a Tong
Lin I mention all this like water
pouring off my body we allow ourselves a
deep renunciation by admitting that
there are these lower realms in a way
extending our compassion and extend me
bring us to these and so start erasing
the idea of doing a meditation for them
to think that these beings are living
simultaneously in the same moment but
having a completely separate reality a
good meditation i neva love the whole
room bring that ultimate deep compassion
for beings who are much much less and so
you know let's go through some of these
six aspects begin 50 let's the
successful satisfaction can be neat so
free always one of mmm always want more
than we have me of Aqaba never satisfied
meet Sophia so Mick Jagger had it right
check off I can't get no satisfaction I
couldn't get no it's pretty self except
the client we always want something else
yeah Mama's on notice say it again
yeah only the good things yeah yeah
that's true when's the last time you
were unsatisfied Munsell freedom at
dinner I don't know like I took the
wrong pasta you know there was the
gluten-free soy macaroni and there was
the no and gluten pesto cheese and I you
know it's like anticipating I love pesto
and cheese I took it and I say it's a
little things big line ending in right
little unsatisfaction declining but the
bigger things are in relationship to our
materialistic reality there's a
statistic take 37 percent of luxury
goods in the world 30 of every Gucci or
Louis Vuitton bag that gets sold in the
world he could cheat a CD of the basic
oft a third of them or more gets sold in
China
little order me ever thinking of a call
you know and a friend of ours had a bag
and she says thousand dollars that could
pay for the acip input Center for a year
and a half it's a piece of leather
I find in China that they've they've
reached a certain place of extraordinary
wealth and materialism because that's
the beginning of what the search the
search for something different that's
not going to disappoint them because you
can only put so many of those in their
closet and you could go to the black
market and buy but in any event I think
we are unsatisfied to some degree next
yeah this is a another depressing of
this must often receive so we yeah we
die over and over again once we cross
the veil we forget everything we ever
learned
nobody clinician spring training that
we're about to embark on it's kind of
like vanish
it's the I was last breath we're gonna
navigate back to Durango to this place
[Music]
that's just so depressing why do we want
to do so the other thing that's
interesting is that we have such
beginningless time experiences of our
death we we've died and shucked off
bodies the size of these mountains and
so what well we certainly can learn and
experience the three principal paths out
and bring everybody with you the whole
game get out and bring everyone with
come back and do it again if you want to
or maybe I mean I know people who have
very clear distinctions of lives that
they've had can can imagine this is gone
I'm gonna leave I'm not gonna III don't
I I think you can develop that practice
[Music]
skipped Elementary and run batted in
then mentioning Triana three three top
deserves our hard drive do comes off the
fest plotted ina Lindley but I
think device because I'm asked for
section sickly Young's you know maybe
it's also a protection to know
commish garnished visible in vocational
valve on hacked away so basically I
found her medication immediately in
common in past lives in our time I'm not
I don't pursue it but I respect people
who think it is an answer there he
respect Erie mentioned loudly martin
finding ricin it doesn't matter really a
basic garland by yet this a moment
humilation of beginning right now in a
tapestry of learning more dharma the
schema dominant yeah ever you've been
god bless you you hear offices you know
got Sigma T's to be steamy lifetimes not
just had the second hour the stew here
height in this model is in the stories
of the Buddha ending Ishida from Buddha
there are so many stories of how many
lifetimes it took him to purify our I
nicked hot as a skilled initiative or
separately
we broke the domain calm immense might
not super raining you know if we did
extremely bad karma many extremely this
comma began in half the easily lead and
our is the super raining it's much more
kind of
comforting to know that you design your
future it's a spelunky NEMA the assumed
understood and it's accomplished I think
ins that would be much more comforting
this is an Guinea moraga donkey why do
we have to take our extension of our own
deep compassion for others bottle miss
Newman Semitic if you love Andre house
women unsworn the Spirit and born why
madam what's the correlation buses buses
the correlation why we why do we want to
just get ourselves out vanish concepts
threatened when bottom we're all in it
together number one I mean we're all
yeah this an island is unwise love this
lateness skip not slightly a tubulin lab
a business or a philosophy did he Sean
Rosen cenarius and did enough train
insane there's no other or our heart
miss captain Veera aha only there there
are only two kinds of beings I skip nuts
wife invasion of decent planning
according to us knock once our
philosophy is one of them's big knocked
Rosen night it's not near and under
alloy stone what Buckton Stas we're in
training to get out get R in yon house
comedy a sincerely component is the
spheres borne off the unmanned mid or
not a menace
risky kind and under ingrown to be most
effective so not suit on under indecent
rice of fellows and use that motivation
DC motivation will allow us to part the
possibility are coming back and teaching
it more in Burton's allowed in suruc su
common mia to Andheri on mentioned
before suma Honda ceiling crisis Allison
cannon does anyone here
do you know your past life is fancy an
indium and an an elite Maradona
yeah cool yeah cool was it a good one
this is Nikhil - yeah crying Oh mawkish
my limbs are hard life wasn't hot this
later okay you see okay that's cool next
we must take birth again and again
dividend keep on V don't we - no murder
press you learn yeah I mean think of the
pain of it thank our ninja man's nice na
da na Mota it's a soul soul schmancer is
coming next runner a nun if I snitched
those memories are in their economy
etiquette surrendering analysis in each
clan their process kept on giving and
mission intense air horn and to hide the
dog and we know a lot of bees friends of
ours everyone in this room I can
guarantee you it is summer I forget to
learn stops to fill in fill in tell the
well this is nice guarantee this is
finito so it's is yes we should we have
the sustainability sir
Venkat hum the song - fortune it's gone
namely we have read it Luke
- Proctor - it's part of who you are
stylist - please - this fiend especially
recent fatality and it's just a mess
he's first in Uganda it's just it's not
ordinary snow my order given thickness
of the name in the snow Martine this is
niched
naman it's extraordinary
also unleash and lowly for still pass so
yeah we don't with a layer number five
muffins
yeah worksheets go up and down over and
over he's an old friend Alicia extending
friend Alicia heard this story time sell
it again a foreign voice and control
factor I told my new movie to my
students today with of course on some
ideas but but detained ec2000 I could
answer doesn't tell his men and chop off
key and I was living in new heaven a
lift and I had worked for its venom it's
a career transmitting antenna and I you
know it was a good company ahead of the
few but they call out a pension plan or
assignment and it shows just threw money
at I thought and they came to 49 is the
soldiers
the company said oh you know
[Music]
so I was like you know and he was
waiting from alloted give up to come
home the house Itsuki called it's your
own such Panasonic
just irresponsible me my smear nice
peanut spit out the fermenting okay
beginning the ha at all shots of
heightened shaking the $50,000 this
tournament four inches look just take a
wild an assistant is report and I post
mini to exciting and he said look cha -
it was his master and he did that that
was a good karma this comma mystic boom
it was very cool court but there it is
right like wow you know I had a those
everything alone so its ups and downs of
this office later health the constant
changing
it's funny you know cause it's always
changing this a Nazi Hema it's next yeah
so John Lennon instinct are my daddy and
one of them is like you can't take
nothing with you but you're so it's the
same thing muscles everything is you can
only take your pseudonym call for coming
to summon a demon you know people that
are in like the day you know under a
hospice care our real speed since the
process of dying he's saying that she
does a couple of dozen most I
my aunt was I went to be with her so I
was you know and I stayed in her room
519 for file a shoe that has for
syndication I couldn't get over
neighbors who were circumstances that
were five or six or eight weeks to live
the guy next to her was simin receive a
steel and he was young this is such a
reality just so at that moment Intel
your seeds just I think your life
Oh in fact and Leah's collapse typical
of you know your mind and guess
completed for standing snake status it's
this kind of situations this is it
that's young because there's nothing
skip need to take absolutely system
intimately man except you're beautiful
so there's one double bond summon you
see and that's what we're here for the
season
this is a projection Charlotte as yeah
yeah we know how to do it yeah it's
profound
it doesn't your house car away beneath
the student house and all of it you know
I don't know just giving everything away
to give me the mostly certificate
[Music]
renunciation is a sweet resonance and
guess the stage in love simply
the sensation of deep dissing
commitments Austin defective in the
process process of getting out
Plus this kind of observation and
renunciation is a special cause that
brings you to what we saw that was a DD
to cosas with vehicle so it's really
that you feel the holiness legal aspect
pushed indignantly to really summon
city workers it occurred in a capacity
you will get see here if I haven't seen
you on questions any questions
it's fun no yes no yes one has a
question he meant identify yeah
Thank You Eli you got a suntan man
listen it's unimportant just don't go
with us I think the for Hammond and if
good to fire you had had in the food
only forget about the fact is if person
D Phi cos Delta sin is fog will happen
if I skip pellets in manova click add on
Selig a Buddhist but isolated evasion
the elephant in a can until they get the
Sun on play on anemic is Palladian
mandolin health and second Indian blood
cystic essentially fanatic and compte
Frogger Varro missus evicted does each a
life that become in another recent self
when they put a spirit selection pellets
yet on am healthy this ambition the
Frogger mr. Sam a technique mo selected
to become and elevators similar to
empower mr. Shah Baba
again the dignity master scene and he's
thanking me the steamed holidays in the
median typical Mennella para it's the
hillford is it becoming Canon like Ian
salmon I split this feeling Ola
oh you mean you don't matter like you
nested together all of us to do the post
alone is interesting the series to human
he can see here yeah it's mostly field
see no after Alan said it sister fire
you seeing them existing Buddhist the
success of this assisted still the
Buddhist same velocity you know for
themselves if you see Silva this man
he's not any recipes except here ask me
skip chunky no glutton in the Kiev at
mercy village oh can you cue again
well let's relate it to our reality shut
the sauce is definitely differently shot
you know if if that's the case in the
Safari status post there is the
possibility just a military person who
is dancing the solutions to fit this
particular citizen specific moment is at
certain moves to stone because I'm not
seeing initially two weeks again is a
mister and that to me is the be
essentially much more going to feel
evolved and if it's just even our and
they're waiting for you to help you know
they know what you're you know if your
beginningless and they know you're
present in your future Buddhist can
identify that they know pretty but they
probably know people another like twenty
years together he'll be with us or
something it's already was into system
they already know that it wasn't ability
we must and this you know become the
fullest evolutionary possibility of this
worse the vodka mind there's nothing
to do other than that because you know
the potential freeze it's exponentially
impossible to even have our minds get it
or get around it the possibility of the
mission of mind
emanating countless bodies probably in
this room for us to perceive as don't
you want to be the I think so and they
don't you're suspicious enough to think
that that question was for you need to
give some kind of an answer for
everybody to hear or something this is
thinking this relation one of the things
that I said earlier today was that in
the Sutra system that our enemies to
have finished look self existent
distance apart from in the esoteric
system it's to see this is the curse
it's the thing we must remove to globe
we have to begin that practice it's not
something that is hardwired we have to
change the sees to get a taste of when
it doesn't become normal
oneness and that you know a question
like that is not you know it gets you
thinking that you know do I sit back and
no then we must in this to see the
extraordinary possibilities Morton
Fullerton guest is an accelerated basis
to saying that's the peak of a
plasticity
this speech and assist mission can be so
we must say that mr. Ennis the mall has
to be killed this normal day ordinary
you see the extra English every day
beautiful name is every single coverage
what get us started I seen that was kept
us see another you know who can I meet
what should i do this morning that boxes
can hurt them how can I apply it to my
all day mindful mind of meditation
freedom does in the morning we will
bring it to them told us in kind of
practice teamwork can help others
skilfully and under there it's just the
mission of what we're all about
does to me she owns dozens thank you
don't get for the I only have
eight yes thank you Kevin fr the
environment from bodhichitta it's been
attributed to sister does he make his
policy the rank and the frankly I'd be
like thinkin can still with the special
American we just meet the directed never
found that I had certain that director
well it's a correlation with the direct
perception of when the for aria to
release yourself which are really did
you absolutely you know this great these
these beautiful colors you're right you
know golden assist assist heroes out of
you out of this deal different beautiful
London and so it it's the other side of
the coin who said that come down off the
doors and that's a similar things that
that the direct experience with the
initiative following from Buddhist you
can you get taste sophistication
absolutely
there's definitely taste and deep
meditation and deformities it sounded
real you know
bank on of them cast off bones it's not
like it's just us but it's not as nice
when you have that expensive song helped
us it doesn't go and get some email and
see different let's just don't touch it
it doesn't go away it's it's there for
the rest day so there's so many
different keeps a few explanations of
bodhichitta and I don't I don't know
them all but I can say that in our
practice Alexi coming practitioners and
have a wish to do that in our you should
be receiving a subtle difference of how
yourself to the sixth most you know an
expression of boat my justice I am not
the same person I was a song different
and my possibility of expanded others
attending us close figure it you know
it's wider I'm seeing the suffering I
let this letter that's a sin more than
myself you know that that's part and
parcel as the evolution of our practice
Alexis and it you know you get those
tasting through your coasters and they
say it is like this artists do it cracks
open its beliefs they say in their
systems this is the the iron vies cracks
open a sentence that's 3/4 of speaking
this do so you can have that
didn't happen tasted a little it
becoming then you know how to navigate
back to it
get in so you know how to go back best
to see that instant you say this we
don't we don't do the Monica okay one
more in the let's do fire to Marvin
ophélie my sister new person
yeah a t-rex kissing hot and see this
sweater do everything it wouldn't bomb
and then put it to it especially it in
say now that era makes them Viet another
sister Nina and they fell over aria yes
there I think it's pretty clear aria
not really no in the earliest stages
about that he said when they just when
they choose the reincarnation of the kid
is spoiled he's just kind of
royalty of a mystic system we get
spoiled
it's like questionable like this really
suddenly around the age of 15 or 16 it's
safe seed start opening over there
actually you know he said that about the
most recent popping Corinth of shades
but when he turned around 60 you know a
real character and no strip but then he
was just such a great debater you saw
this enormous ripen
the teacher I have he you know the the
direct perception of emptiness can have
them eternal again is something most
seen it was just once the next slide
they dumped him put you back in there
you see and also in the direct
perception of emptiness you see while
you're gonna get a lot of I had see
stuff on there actually you actually see
this is the spirit justice if when it's
going to be how many yeah thank you
thank you then thank you for you know
thank you soon one more I'll go handle
it Safari okay
yeah silly question
yep the fog limit and smile had we met
on turbo boost and this eventful as news
that's what yeah last night this right
Canyon you have to skip so it wasn't
give spirit some bashful Heart
Assocation actually have it as a crank
us at Alexis and Hammond put each it
finished off kibosh this by unity yeah
can I put it on a condom infinitive and
bikini for him tolik advocate anything
yeah but if you think you can unless
connect a man yeah I you know that's
something that we're all dealing with
for me it's CSIS this meditation it
really is like you start with you know
Tumlin I mean start with one human being
who is animation Sepphoris myths and we
all know that beginning do it you know
you embody the feeling about this
country and those deep different coasts
and you literally are investing in is
just a journey to take their assistive
that must give you results to help the
suffering of being even see that person
but you can help so that's just a simple
example we underestimate the power of
that practice it was a secret
but it has the power is how she left
understand emptiness of possibility your
seeds easily wanting to helped us you
see it changes to see them in this okay
fetter and so that's and we start sunny
Davis says start with the tears and
tears don't start with you know you know
I don't know you know thinking that you
can save start small use practices
meditation and then take it into the
world few little things for he must
learn the rejoicing of the tiny studio
empty that we don't have credit
ourselves having somebody opening up a
door or any of these tiny little things
like make them because think
they can generate some hits
that's somebody's dead thank you so much
thank you feedback